Using Unity and for China XR.
GMT in our present.
Dragon Shot.
Face off against a giant
dragon using immersive motion
controlled artery in HKO's
cave environment.
Using a hand tracker and controller,
players physically draw, aim and fire
arrows for natural artery emotions.
To damage the dragon first
destroy the magic crystals
protecting the dragon won't
stay passive.
It launches deadly fire balls
that must be shot down
before they can reach you.
Once the shield is broken,
the dragon becomes vulnerable.
This is your chance to
destroy the dragon.
Take aim and don't hold back.
New players can use a Tetra tree
P field to assess their age.
For a greater challenge,
disable the scope and
rely entirely on skill.
Multiple difficulties levels
alter the dragon's speed
crystal count and attack
patterns.
In hard mode, destroyed crystals
regenerate after twenty seconds,
leaving only a brief window
to strike the dragon.
Can you defeat a dragon on
hard mode before the scope?
Try it for yourself.